- Okay, one more time?
- Never mind, you won't get it right.
(Sheldon:)I'd better come with you.
(Penny:)Oh, yay.
(Penny:)How come
you didn't go in to work today?
(Sheldon:)I'm taking a sabbatical because
I won't kowtow to mediocre minds.
(Penny:)So you got canned, huh?
(Sheldon:)Theoretical physicists do not get canned.
(Sheldon:)But, yeah.
Maybe it's for the best.
You know, I always say, "When one door
closes, another one opens."
(Sheldon:)No, it doesn't.
Not unless the doors
are connected by relays.
(Sheldon:)- Or there are motion sensors involved.
- No, I meant...
Or if the first door closing creates a change
of air pressure that acts upon the second.
(Sheldon:)Never mind.
(Sheldon:)Slow down. Slow down.
Please, slow down.
(Penny:)We're fine.
(Sheldon:)You're not leaving
enough space between cars.
(Penny:)Oh, sure I am.
(Sheldon:)No, no, let me do the math for you.
This car weighs, let's say, 4000 pounds.